Stop the Green Goliath... At all costs
Hulk vs. Wolverine is a animation, action, science
fiction film directed by Frank Paur.
Department H sends in Wolverine to track down a mysterious beast known by the US
Military as the Hulk, who is rampaging across the Canadian wilderness.
Surveying the extent of the damage to a destroyed town, Wolverine
notices a toxic scent as well as the smell of gunpowder.
He is then deployed to the wilderness to resume tracking the creature.
Hulk (voice), played by Fred Tatasciore.
Bruce Banner (voice), played by Bryce Johnson.
Wolverine / Logan (voice), played by Steve Blum.
Deadpool (voice), played by Nolan North.
The Professor (voice), played by Tom Kane.
Lady Deathstrike (voice), played by Janyse Jaud.
Marvel Animated Features (MAF) is a series of eight American direct-to-video animated superhero films made by MLG
Productions, a joint venture between Marvel Studios (later Marvel Animation) and Lions Gate Entertainment.
The film explores themes of superhero, mutant, based on comic, norse mythology.
The tone is thought_provoking.